Guide to the Vassar College Dean of the Faculty Records, 1901-2009
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IV. Faculty Load Records, 1901-1970
  - 1933-1934 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1934-1935 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1935-1936 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1936-1937 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1937-1938 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1938-1939 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1939-1940 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1940-1941 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1941-1942 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1942-1943 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1943-1944 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1944-1945 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1945-1946 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1946-1947 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1947-1948 (Box 43 (Box 2))
  - 1948-1949 (Box 44 (Box 3))
  - 1949-1950 (Box 44 (Box 3))
  - 1950-1951 (Box 44 (Box 3))
  - 1951-1952 (Box 44 (Box 3))
  - 1952-1953 (Box 44 (Box 3))
  - 1953-1954 (Box 44 (Box 3))
  - 1954-1955 (Box 45 (Box 4))
  - 1955-1956 (Box 45 (Box 4))
  - 1956-1957 (Box 45 (Box 4))
  - 1957-1958 (Box 45 (Box 4))
  - 1958-1959 (Box 45 (Box 4))
  - 1959-1960 (Box 45 (Box 4))
  - 1960-1961 (Box 45 (Box 4))
  - 1961-1962 (Box 45 (Box 4))
  - 1962-1963, (2 folders) (Box 45 (Box 4))
  - 1963-1964 (Box 46 (Box 5))
  - 1964-1965 (Box 46 (Box 5))
  - 1965-1966 (Box 46 (Box 5))
  - 1966-1967, (3 folders) (Box 46 (Box 5))
  - 1969-1970 (Box 46 (Box 5))
  - Faculty load reference, reports, and indexes, 1950-1959 (Box 46 (Box 5))
  - Reports to the Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees, 1948-1957 (Box 46 (Box 5))